So great to meet you.
You're here to pitch me.
Pitch.
Yes.
It's a parody of the movie Giant.
But instead, our James Dean character strikes
it rich in cum instead of oil.
So imagine long
panoramic orgy scenes, torrid love affairs.
I mean, we're talking mass market appeal.
Mass market appeal.
Um. And it's a musical.
And you want to make this with my money.
I'm gonna need a little something upfront.
Give me taste.
No! Get me a demo.
No, that's not available.
That's not available
either.
No.
We'll contact you if anything changes?
Not.
You have lunch with Bradly at 2, and your
Brazilian's scheduled for 4:30, sir.
OK. Did you reconsile last quarter?
Yes.
Did you send out affiliate checks?
Did you clean the fridge?
Yes.
Walk the dog?
Did you get that dress I looked at online?
Yes.
Red or blue?
Yes and yes.
Did you get the dubbing for the
Spanish language movie?
Si.
Did you get the one for the German?
Ja.
Russian.
Da.
French?
Oui.
Japanese.
Hai.
World Peace?
Yeah.
Tickets for this show Saturday?
Yes.
You are efficient!
All right. You said you did the laundry.
That means clean sheets!
You may be wondering why you're sitting
here in the hot seat.
Do you know why you're adorable?
No...
Could it be because you're smart.
Maybe.
Could it be... Where's your, where's your belt?
I'm trying to be smooth here.
Could it be because...you are perty?
Maybe.
Could it be because
you're talented?
Maybe.
Could it be because you're just a horny, slutty
girl?
Probably.
Really? I like horny slutty girls.
You have been so good and
so efficient.
That you get extra sex time.
That's what you get for getting your work done
early.
You trying to find my zipper?
You bad girl.
My, what clever fingers you have.
Get comfy for spankies.
Ooh, your
jewelry is showing so beautifully.
Oh, I'll go harder
don't worry.
I know this is nothing for you. [spanks]
Oh, I could smell your pussy from here you
horny, girl.
Were
you looking at porn at work?
Were you looking at
Pink and White movies.
Are you a dirty girl.
So beautiful Sara.
[spankings] .
Where was I? I was giving you a beautiful
rub.
Your beautiful bits.
Here she is.
Hi, clit.
So tight, that's two.
I can barely fit two fingers in your cookie,
sweetheart.
How's that big red dildo gonna fit in that little
tight hole anyway?
We can try!
What happens if I crawl up
here, and put on another glove. And lean back, and played
with your pussy. While you did that.
Wouldn't that be fun?
Oh god, you're so good at that. Did you
go to school for that?
Did you do that at college?
You're so good to that sweetheart.
[laughs]
What are we going to do with you?
Do I get to fuck you?
Is that it? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Back to my glass.
Luckily.
Oh, that will definitely do it.
Hi Pretty. Best assistant.
You just need to get fucked don't you.
Assume the position.
Oh so that was the right spot.
Oh,
oh,
oh.
Pretty princess.
Oh, oh,
oh, oh.
You like my leg, rubbing my pussy on your leg? Humping on you?
Oh, oh.
Oh, I sure like humping your leg.
Oh,
oh, oh,
oh,
oh my.
I wish you could see what I'm seeing.
Pretty pussy.
Taking this toy
all the way in.
Oh, my
dick's turning round.
Oh,
yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, oh.
Oh.
My ball's are coming out.
Go back in. Silly toy.
There we go.
Oh, oh, oh,
oh.
Do
you like looking at that?
Oh, oh,
oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh,
You get a full orgasm seeling how you've been so
amazing, you did all of the amazing things for
me.
You deserve all  the reward.
Oh, oh.
Yeah.
That's right.
Oh, whoa, oh,
oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh.
Oh sure.
Okay.
Oh.
Oh yeah.
God I love
seeing that toy disappearance inside of you. It's so hot.
Rubbing on my clit.
Oh oh oh
oh oh
oh oh oh
oh.
Grind against it. Yah. Ah, that pushes it against my clit, too.
Put your hand on your clit, sweetheart? are
you ready for the buzzy thing?
Yeah.
Oh here we go.
You gotta hold to yourself because I don't know where you like it. [vibrator buzzes on]
Oh, hello.
Hi.
Hi there.
Aaah.
Line it up from the clit,
there it goes.
Oh oh
oh oh
oh
oh.
Oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh,
oh,
oh. [vibrator silences]
Oh, my goodness gracious.
Every week. I know what it is
that I hired you.
We
need to get a boy, I'll let you place
that ad, then you can do all the interviews.
Hello boobies. Boobie one.
Mm mm mm
mm mm mm mm mm
mm mm mm.
Is it true, people are more sensitive after
they've come?
I'm not going to hit her. Don't worry.
Can't be hitting pussies with jewelry.
Hi beauty.
How are you? Happier now?
I'm happier now.
I want to do a little more.
Okay! Fingers, Toy?
What would you like?
Penetration?
Oh, a little bit, maybe with your hand.
Oh, yes.
Oh, boy, oh, boy.
Oh, golly, I'd like some more, please.
You don't get more.
Actually in my world you get as much as you can
have.
Yeah.
Do you like fingers up or fingers down?
Uhh...
Uppy? Downy...
Maybe downy. [Vibrator buzzes]
Take it away for a second.
Okey doke.
Moving or just pressure?
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
O o
o o o.
O o o o
o.
Take your fingers out?
Oooh, fuck... [vibrator silences]
You're lucky I don't have ice cubes... Hello beautiful.
Are we gonna to give it the green light?
We?